

SOFTWARE ARCHITECT · SECURITY EXPERT

42-8, Bangbae-ro 15-gil, Seocho-gu, Seoul, 00681, Rep. of KOREA

[(+82) 10-9030-1843 | ■ posquit0.bj@gmail.com | 😭 www.posquit0.com | 🖸 posquit0 | 🛅 posquit0

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

Summary

A self-motivated developer with 2+ years of experience in a fast-paced leading educational startup and continuously striving to expand skill sets. Proficient in Python/Django and learning new programming languages like Golang. Aspiring to be part of a team that solves problems using technology and learn new things. Have a bachelor's degree in Computer Science.

Experience

Entri.me Ernakulam, Kerala

PRODUCT ENGINEER Feb. 2015 - Present

Entri, is Cochin based product startup that provides a Plug and Play learning system for teachers and students in India. 23,000 students, 400 teachers, and 32 institutes have used Entri to improve their learning and teaching so far. Entri is the first company from India to get selected into LearnLaunch in Boston, USA.

- One of the initial employees
- Designed a payment processing system and integrated with Payumoney and Razorpay for processing the payments
- Integrated with SendGrid for transactional emails and Mvaayoo for transactional SMS
- Designed and implemented REST APIs to support entri.me Android Application
- Developed responsive web applications with Bootstrap and Sass preprocessor

Recupated dashboard to track and analyse student performance for teachers

Ernakulam, Kerala

SOFTWARE TRAINEE March. 2014 - Jan. 2015

Mentorship program to become a better programmer by reading books, writing code, participating in Massive Open Online Courses (MOOC) and pursuing personal projects.

- Used GNU/Linux Operating System from day 1 and did Python based projects and programming assignments.
- Gained exposure in developing web applications using Python based frameworks like Django and Flask

Honors & Awards.

INTERNATIONAL

2018	Finalist, DEFCON 26th CTF Hacking Competition World Final	Las Vegas, U.S.A
2017	Finalist, DEFCON 25th CTF Hacking Competition World Final	Las Vegas, U.S.A
2014	Finalist, DEFCON 22nd CTF Hacking Competition World Final	Las Vegas, U.S.A
2013	Finalist, DEFCON 21st CTF Hacking Competition World Final	Las Vegas, U.S.A
2011	Finalist, DEFCON 19th CTF Hacking Competition World Final	Las Vegas, U.S.A

DOMESTIC

2015	3rd Place , WITHCON Hacking Competition Final	Seoul, S.Korea
2017	Silver Prize, KISA HDCON Hacking Competition Final	Seoul, S.Korea
2013	Silver Prize, KISA HDCON Hacking Competition Final	Seoul, S.Korea

Presentation

DevFest Seoul by Google Developer Group Korea

Seoul, S.Korea

PRESENTER FOR < HOSTING WEB APPLICATION FOR FREE UTILIZING GITHUB, NETLIFY AND CLOUDFLARE>

Nov. 2017

- · Introduced the history of web technology and the JAM stack which is for the modern web application development.
- Introduced how to freely host the web application with high performance utilizing global CDN services.

PRESENTER FOR < DEFCON 20TH: THE WAY TO GO TO LAS VEGAS>

Jul. 2012

· Introduced CTF(Capture the Flag) hacking competition and advanced techniques and strategy for CTF

Writing.

A Guide for Developers in Start-up

Facebook Page

FOUNDER & WRITER

Jan. 2015 - PRESENT

• Drafted daily news for developers in Korea about IT technologies, issues about start-up.

Program Committees

2016 **Problem Writer**, 2016 CODEGATE Hacking Competition World Final

S.Korea

2013 Organizer & Co-director, 1st POSTECH Hackathon

S.Korea

Education

Lourdes Matha College of Science and Technology

Kerala University

B.TECH IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

Mar. 2009 - 2013

• Organised inter college computer science fest

Extracurricular Activity

PoApper (Developers' Network of POSTECH)

Pohang, S.Korea

CORE MEMBER & PRESIDENT AT 2013

Jun. 2010 - Jun. 2017

- Reformed the society focusing on software engineering and building network on and off campus.
- Proposed various marketing and network activities to raise awareness.

PLUS (Laboratory for UNIX Security in POSTECH)

Pohang, S.Korea

MEMBER

Sep. 2010 - Oct. 2011

- Gained expertise in hacking & security areas, especially about internal of operating system based on UNIX and several exploit techniques.
- Participated on several hacking competition and won a good award.
- Conducted periodic security checks on overall IT system as a member of POSTECH CERT.
- Conducted penetration testing commissioned by national agency and corporation.

March 2, 2021 Byungjin Park · Résumé 2